

### ABOUT ME

Experienced software developer with 3 years of experience building and developing web applications for pharmaceutical and construction companies. Holding a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, and a diploma in Frontend Development from the school of Hyper Island.

### LANGUAGES (#)

• English: Fluent • Swedish: Basic • French: Basic • Arabic: Native

### CERTIFICATES Q

- MCSD: Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer (Share-Point+Web Applications)
- YAT Professional Diploma In Web Design
- SFI-Level C

## REFERENCES ╩

Erik Sturesson, Manager at Student Node erik.sturesson@studentnode.com

May Jutrakul, Program Manager and Supervisor at Hyper Island rada.jutrakul@hyperisland.com

# IRINI IBRAHIM

#### Frontend Developer, BSc in Computer Science

@ irini.ibrahim@hyperisland.se

**+**46790762045

Stockholm, Sweden

☐ Irinilbrahim

in irini-ibrahim-74338199

**#** 1991/06/06

### WORK EXPERIENCE 🖴

#### Frontend Developer intern Student Node

iii October 2023 - April 2024

Stockholm, Sweden

#### **Senior Software Developer**

Red Sea Construction, Building and Development

**April** 2017 - June 2018

Cairo, Egypt

#### **Software Specialist - Application Development** Global NAPI Pharmaceuticals

**Tanuary** 2016 - March 2017

Cairo, Egypt

#### **Customer Service Agent** CitiBank Egypt and CIB

December 2014 - December 2015

Cairo, Egypt

### **EDUCATION**

### Frontend Development Diploma

The school of Hyper Island

**August 2022 - March 2024** 

Stockholm, Sweden

#### Swedish for Programmers SFX-IT

**a** January 2021 - June 2021

Stockholm, Sweden

#### E-commerce (.NET Development)

Ministry of Communications and Information Technology (MCIT)

**2013 - 2014** 

Cairo, Egypt

#### **Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science**

Higher Institute of Computer and Information Technology, El Shorouk Academy

**2009 - 2013** 

Cairo, Egypt

• Graduation project: Website Auto Building (Grade: Excellent).

# PROGRAMMING & SOFTWARE SKILLS </>

• React.js

VB. Net

• Electron.js

Javascript

VS Code

UX/UI design

TypeScript

• Git

Reporting services

HTML5/CSS3

OOP

Node.js

• SQL

• Tailwind/css

Express.js

Bootstrap

SharePoint

Alpine js

C#

DevExpress

Material UI

JQuery - AJAX

Jira

Linux

• ASP.NET Core/MVC

• Entity framework

• Three.js

Figma

• Agile framework

GSAP

• Adobe tools: Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Animate, Bridge, Muse.